hello everyone today I wanted to give a
little update in regards to how the home
is turning out when I first moved in
here I kind of put Furniture everywhere
but since then we've decided to do some
Renovations and change some things and
so it definitely still feels like we're
moving in and I was waiting to show you
a more completed picture of the home but
I decided why not to show you kind of
where we're at right now maybe I can get
some good ideas from you and thankfully
my husband is here today so he is the
cameraman I contrary to popular belief I
filmed my own videos most of the time he
is just helping today so I am very
grateful too so thank you love you're
welcome all right I thought I would
start in kind of the main part of the
house where I spend the most time in and
this is the living room and it is
definitely one of my favorite places I
picked quite a few flowers just to
celebrate this occasion so
these go back
and this is where you like to watch your
historical dramas and more movies oh yes
maybe some zombie movies sometimes you
know mix it up with the little My Little
Pony yes and princess movies
because I'm a child this uh is
definitely one of my favorite pieces of
furniture because even though I don't
use the TV I like how elegantly it can
be kind of tucked away so I really enjoy
that and then I clearly have a lot of
plants
so uh so many of them
and I thought I'd tell you a secret if
you ever want to have your room feel
like it's just full of plants and it
feels green and alive but you struggle
to find the time to water every single
one of them you can get fake plants from
a thrift store usually there are quite a
few there and you can mix them in with
the real ones I think my other favorite
way to have plants is in jars I think
that's one of my favorites I think
they're just so unique and I like the
little terrariums
and you can just show all the details
here if you don't mind love I love to
hang all sorts of little
Creations from the windows you made this
mm-hmm
he finds he finds crystals up in the
mountains and then he does wire wrapping
and wire weaving and he he made that
and then he also made this beautiful
fascinator
and it has little bunnies with wings
because of course because he knows me
very well
and
it's just one of my favorite things in
this entire house I love having little
decals of birds on the window I think it
helps deter actual birds from running
into the window and
I also really enjoy these curtains
I found these ones they were fairly
affordable very airy and light and if
you ever want your
house to feel like a Whimsical fairy
Cottage you can always get little
butterflies and attach them to anywhere
they can possibly go and then when
people walk in they can be really
concerned about your taste so anyway
more little things here I have quite a
few decorations that are from
subscribers
such as these someone sent me a set of
these and yeah there's quite a few
little things that a lot of you have
sent me so I really really appreciate
that
we have uh some cat toys on the floor
you know because
there's a cat somewhere she's hiding
this is another favorite Nook of mine
because I incorporate it often in videos
I love my little stove I have decorated
it of course with some summer flowers
because I just think that really
brightens up the space when it's not in
use and I used to love just actual wood
burning stoves and I love the feel and
the smell of it but I have to admit I
really like the gas stoves they're so
much easier to clean and you don't have
to spend all summer chopping wood which
is really really lovely so I like too
that it keeps the air in the house a lot
cleaner so I really appreciate that and
of course I made some decorations
I am a watercolorist and so I like to
spend quite a bit of time working on my
art pieces
always trying to uh think of new aspects
of nature to portray plants more plants
there's just so many of them
um yes and this is just the main couch
it is definitely
one we use quite a bit when I got it I
was a little concerned because I saw
that it was this very bright blue and it
just wasn't what I thought it was gonna
look like from the pictures online which
I think is always the case and so I
actually just got this couch sized throw
to put over it and then this one as well
so if you ever have a couch that is not
quite the right color or the right look
that you were expecting then there's
always a solution because there was no
way I was gonna buy another one because
it would have been too expensive so
that's kind of how we've made it work I
think I said every corner of this part
of the house is my favorite but this is
actually my favorite for a reason you
will soon understand
it is the library oh and this is the
main door as well and we would love to
get this door replaced at some point
that is a huge goal it is just kind of
one of the cheapest stores you can kind
of get and I would love to have like a
really nice door for the fun of the
house someday that would be lovely but
they are so expensive so that's
definitely years away and right now it's
a bit of a Daydream but so far I've
really enjoyed this little mantelpiece
on top that just has all these little
what would you call it doodads some of
these things are from subscribers
and so they've sent them to me and
they're all very special
these are also some other things I've
been given by subscribers such as
candles and this little embroidered
piece uh this little dish here I got
when I was a child in a thrift store in
Wallace Idaho and it was just one of my
favorite things that is from Japan and
it was like two dollars I think my my
dad got it for me
then here I have more plants and more
books I have too many books at any given
moment so you know that's just kind of
an ongoing issue but I will do a more
detailed like every single book I own if
you would like to see that I'm more than
happy to talk about books but someday so
if you let me know if you'd like to see
a detailed bookshelf tour because I I
could definitely do that so
so there are definitely a lot of plants
here a lot of these art pieces so I
thought it would give you a little bit
of insight on how I like to think when
I'm decorating and one is that I knew
that the walls are going to be this kind
of sage green
with a little bit of blue and I also
thought that because of the artist's
color wheel
complementary colors to Green are red
tones and so that's one of the reasons
Christmas is so appealing the uh tones
of green and red together and so that's
why I got kind of a red blanket to go
with a more green wall so that's often
what I'm thinking about when I'm
decorating I like to think about how
colors work together and then also throw
those all those rules out of the window
whenever you know doesn't work so and
just do whatever you want but that is at
least a little bit of insight on what I
like to do anyway here are it's just my
bookshelf Luke was so lovely to make
this he is so talented and I love the
raw wood edges
it's just one of my favorite things and
it's so unique and I just I mean there's
never going to be any other bookshelf
exactly like this and I think that's so
special just to have something so
beautifully made
well down here I just have kind of this
little area where I can sit and work on
projects if I want to I love this chair
I actually found it on the side of the
road it is a chair that belonged to an
artist and on under it it says it was uh
refurbished in the 90s so it's quite an
old chair and you can tell if you look
up close it you know it's it's pretty
old but we don't need to look too close
to it but I really like how it looks
it's such a unique design
so if you know what style of chair this
is do let me know I'd love to find
another one in this style
but yeah I absolutely love it
so yes there's just a lot of little tiny
details all around these bookshelves and
I'll try to do close-ups of all of them
later so you can just get a feel and
here is one of my very favorite
paintings subscribers have sent me all
sorts of paintings this one was one that
was sent to me a while ago
and it was right after I lost my rabbit
Mr Darcy and so it's very special
I think that is everything so I think
instead I can just show you the upstairs
of the house which is definitely what's
a lot more in progress I'll show you a
little more of the kitchen before I go
upstairs but the kitchen's pretty boring
so honey
Mommy
hi honey
all right so this is the kitchen area it
is quite simple I just have some flowers
out here for decoration I love to have
candles in here as well because this
tends to be the darkest part of the
house especially in the winter time so
hopefully you can see some of the
details so one detail I like to do on
houses
to just make them a little bit more
special is just to add these switch
plates into make them quite decorative
and interesting so it's just a little
thing but I think it just adds a really
unique touch to a home because most
people never think about switch plates
so that was just an idea that one I
think is ceramic they they um tend to
not be that expensive I budgeted for
them for
a while but um
but yeah I really like how this looks so
here is my collection of tea of course I
have tea pretty much every single day
and I would love to have a vintage oven
and a vintage microwave but those are
very expensive and don't tend to work
well so we're going modern here so it's
a lot more practical and it is what was
already in the house so we just have
over here we have the kind of dining
area
right now we have a really worn out
table that desperately needs to be
sanded and repainted
and it's just definitely yeah it it
looks like we picked it up at a thrift
store which we did we did how big my mom
did yeah so there you go but yeah I
think with the new coat of paint I think
it's going to look lovely and hopefully
we can find two more chairs that match
so over here I also like to
put all the dried flowers
that I have been harvesting throughout
the year I just like to leave them up
there I think they look lovely and now
and then I then come up with a use for
them usually I use them as a wreath or
something like that and so yeah I really
enjoy this part of the house I just wish
it got a little bit more light because
it is quite dark in here and then here
we have a monstrosity of coats and shoes
mostly mine yeah sorry about that Luca
works as a surveyor and he's Outdoors
all day working really hard so he's
allowed to put his boots in his coats
anywhere he wants I also got this piece
of furniture it was quite inexpensive
but it's great for just taking off your
shoes and I will show up close shots of
the carpets I did get those for Fairly
inexpensive too a new discovery that I
had in this house is barn doors and how
beautiful I think they are I love these
stores that just slide back instead of
opening and this just leads to a
bathroom so in the washing machine so
it's really lovely to dry clothes
outside in the summer when you know the
sun could disinfect it but uh definitely
you know when it's very dirty or in the
winter definitely washing machines
become even more useful so now we're
gonna go upstairs to the part of the
house that is in progress
and still being renovated so all right
Luke is doing this on a Saturday and
it's really nice of them to be doing
this I'm trying better I don't feel like
I'm doing the greatest job oh
I think it's everything so maybe that
can be some inspiration for you to think
about upcycling recycling using old you
know items and just revamping them I
take a lot more pride in things that I
create you know when I really put time
and energy into them so that's just an
idea for you so I'm not gonna open this
door just because it's a small room and
I just have the bunnies in there they
spend the night in there for safety so
that nothing goes after them during the
night but they also have outdoor uh
Little Homes but Luke is also building a
large Sanctuary enclosure for them as
well so I will show you clips of all
that for sure all right so we can go up
here
this this part of the house feels quite
plain to me I've just put up a few
little things like some orange garlands
I always wanted a piece of stained glass
I think stained glass is such a
beautiful art form and I could never
afford one because they're they're so
expensive and this was from my
grandfather's home after he passed away
his things inside his home were being
given away and this stained glass piece
was left and so I thought I just had to
put something
from his home and and here and I just
think it looks so beautiful
so this is the room that probably about
a year ago you saw completely furnished
and now it is empty because we are
trying to move the bedroom in here so
that there can be one little spare room
for an office space or future family and
yeah this is just definitely a work in
progress so if if you have any
decorating ideas for this part of the
house let me know
but this is going to be a closet right
that's what you're building here yeah
and then there's going to be
a bed here and hopefully it will all
turn into a really lovely master bedroom
someday
but that is a work in progress for sure
over here is a little bathroom
it's very simple it's just there's
nothing nothing to it
it is very minimal
I would love to decorate it but I've
just decided to wait because I want to
hopefully have this to be an office
space at some point
and I do have some of my paintings and
one little shelf here
and I also have just some shelves full
of all sorts of little items that have
been either gifts for birthday Christmas
or I found at Medieval fairs
all sorts of unique interesting things
foreign
[Music]
so here is just the porch
it is again another spot I use
frequently
I have planted quite a few plants they
have a hard time surviving during the
winter because it gets so cold and snowy
here so my plan is to just have these
for now and then put them in the ground
in the fall
so hopefully they make it through the
winter
and so I love to sit up here and read my
book and just listen to the birds and
the rain
and if you ever want some
fun ideas for decorating you might want
to use
Bells I love hanging Bells everywhere
and um yeah so I also have these Vines
here they've been flowering all spring
and summer which has just been such a
gift they are so happy here
foreign
and I just have some random wildflowers
growing in here I don't know what's
happening but I hope you enjoyed this
this was the whole house for the most
part except for one tiny room and
um yeah you could hopefully get a feel
for where we're at right now I really
want to do a little bit more changes and
improvements um there's definitely a lot
of little things that need to be fixed
but it's an ongoing process and so far
I've been really enjoying it and we're
excited for the future so if you if you
have any decoration ideas do please let
me know and I will see you all very soon
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I hope you enjoyed that home tour it's
been really fun to be working on this
space I will not show my pet housing
situation yet because it is a work in
progress we're trying to build this
outdoor you know Arena area for them and
so I will give an update on all of that
very soon but I wanted to put it all in
one video please leave questions down
below thank you so so much for watching
I appreciate all the support of my work
as an artist and my Etsy Shop it keeps
this channel going I do not put mid-roll
ads in these videos neither do I do
sponsorships and part of the reason that
I'm able to keep from doing those things
is due to my work as an artist and so
that means the world thank you and I
will finish on one note that I think it
is very important to know that I did of
course tidy up my home before filming
this things will get cluttered or dirty
or you know just normal life happens so
do keep that in mind when watching this
video also the things in your home are
great I am an artist I love items that I
have found on my Adventures outdoors I
have a lot of nature a lot of plants all
these things are wonderful but what
really makes a home a home to me is the
memories and the thoughts and ideas and
feelings you bring into it I think that
is why you know when I work on my own
self and I'm able to sustain a feeling
of more peace and less stress my home
feels better it's not about the things
in it of course we should all love to
express ourselves I love art I will
always decorate my home but it is not
what makes my home special to me it is
that coziness it is that feeling of
safety and it is my own self and how I'm
feeling projected into my surroundings I
think that is often how many of us
function with that being said I hope you
can take a moment to enjoy your own
place of shelter it is such a gift to
have a roof over your head at any point
and I appreciate you being here I'm
sending you so much love goodbye
foreign
[Music]